<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookApp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_advance">AdvanceActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="bottom_text">
        <item>       Book lookup App; Notes
        \n This demo app was intended for testing purposes only. While fully functional for what it is,
        I intended to use it as grounds for testing features and functions that would a good addition
        to such an app.
        \n\n The following are features or implementations that were required for this app to work.</item>
 <item>        \n\n <b>Adapters and POJO class</b>
        \n The POJO class contained the get and setter methods (setters not used.) The Adapter was used
        to implement the listView and update it to show results from the public Google Books API.</item>
<item>        \n\n <b>AsyncTask and Loaders</b>
        \n AsyncTask was initially used to stop the downloading/UI updater from hogging up the main thread,
        thus pause the app of all functionality during its runtime. AsyncTask presented an issue where
        a destroy() would cause the app to onCreate() all over again and thus go back to loading. This issue
        was fixed using Loader Managers and AsyncTaskLoaders. Now a recreate such as screen rotation will
        no longer require redownload and subsequent UI updates.</item>
<item>        \n\n <b>Animation, TranslationAnimation, and ObjectAnimator</b>
        \n Used to update the UI via the "advanced" button located on the top right of the screen.
        Animation was used for light animation such as the editText's slight movements while no text is
        present. TranslationAnimation was used for the onscreen item shifts. The issue presented was
        that the TranslationAnimation would cause the view to visibly move from it's original position to
        the new position, but its essence and functionality remained where it initially was as oppose to the new position.
        A remedy for this was an listener to figure out when the view was done with its moves and shift the UI.
        This however caused the animation to flickr before reaching its destination. ObjectAnimator, the newer
        of the bunch along with overrides of its onFinish, onStart and other methods, did what the other two were not able
        to do.</item>
<item>        \n\n <b>Settings and SharedPreferences</b>
        \n The changes and requirements of the app's small footprint did not require the need for a larger
        database such as an SQLite table. Instead, a sharedPreferences was the preference here to store key/value
        pairs to allow users to have more choice with the app. The settings page demonstrates changing themes
        dynamically along with updating the UI to reflect theme or option changes. SharedPreferences was used
</item>


    </string>


    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
</resources>
